wallpaperama.com 2007-04-23

# Free Wallpapers - Pravacy Statement

**Wallpaperama.com Privacy Policy**  

**wallpaperama.com** has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site.

**Advertisers  
** Third Party Advertising  
We May third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please click here.

Third Party Cookies  
In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser.

**Personal Information**  
This Web site does allow user to enter their email address at their own will for subscription in our newsletter. We do not request any personal information or collect any information that personally identifies you or allows you to be personally contacted.

Since we do not collect any personal information on this Web site, we do not share any personal information with any third parties nor do we use any personal information for any purposes.

** Use of Cookies:
**
wallpaperama.com employ cookies in order to allow us to know if user have the site software "Cool Wallpaper Software" installed so that users can download photo from us. We do not use cookies to track user activities in anyway. In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique “cookie” on your browser.

**External Links**  
This site contains links to other sites. **_[wallpaperama.com](http://wallpaperama.com/)_** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

**Contacting the Web Site**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact: [webmaster@wallpaperama.com](mailto:webmaster@wallpaperama.com)
